https://www.ctbank.com/privacy.aspx

GO
Home+COVID-19 RESOURCESCBA Member BanksNon-Member BanksReopening Resources+About UsMission StatementExecutive CommitteeWho To ContactDirections+MembershipMembership BenefitsMember Bank DirectoryAssociate Member DirectoryMembers Only+EducationWebinarsWomen In BankingBankWorldCenter for Financial TrainingSeminar StatusMember Registration Links+CSFMFAQ'sClass of 2021 & 2022 Class ScheduleCSFM FacultyApplication+CBA QuarterlyBanking Magazine+Products & ServicesCBA Endorsed Providers+Bankers AllianceCompliance AllianceReview Alliance+ClassifiedsSubmit Job OpeningEmployment Legal LineCT Most Wanted+News RoomPress Releases & AnnouncementsGeneral Bulletins
|
Login
HomeCOVID-19 RESOURCESCBA Member BanksNon-Member BanksReopening ResourcesAbout UsMission StatementExecutive CommitteeWho To ContactDirectionsMembershipMembership BenefitsMember Bank DirectoryAssociate Member DirectoryMembers OnlyEducationWebinarsWomen In BankingBankWorldCenter for Financial TrainingSeminar StatusMember Registration LinksCSFMFAQ'sClass of 2021 & 2022 Class ScheduleCSFM FacultyApplicationCBA QuarterlyBanking MagazineProducts & ServicesCBA Endorsed ProvidersBankers AllianceCompliance AllianceReview AllianceClassifiedsSubmit Job OpeningEmployment Legal LineCT Most WantedNews RoomPress Releases & AnnouncementsGeneral Bulletins
Privacy Statement
Connecticut Bankers Association is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the Connecticut Bankers Association Web site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the Connecticut Bankers Association website, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Connecticut Bankers Association collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Connecticut Bankers Association also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by Connecticut Bankers Association. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This
information is used by Connecticut Bankers Association for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the Connecticut Bankers Association Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through Connecticut Bankers Association public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Connecticut Bankers Association
does not read any of your private online communications.
Connecticut Bankers Association encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from Connecticut Bankers Association so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. Connecticut Bankers Association is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Connecticut Bankers Association
and Connecticut Bankers Association family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Connecticut Bankers Association collects and uses your personal information to operate the Connecticut Bankers Association
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Connecticut Bankers Association also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Connecticut Bankers Association and its affiliates. Connecticut Bankers Association may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
Connecticut Bankers Association does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Connecticut Bankers Association may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Connecticut Bankers Association
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to Connecticut Bankers Association, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
Connecticut Bankers Association does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Connecticut Bankers Association keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
Connecticut Bankers Association, in order to determine what Connecticut Bankers Association services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within Connecticut Bankers Association to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Connecticut Bankers Association Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on Connecticut Bankers Association or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Connecticut Bankers Association; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Connecticut Bankers Association, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Connecticut Bankers Association Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Connecticut Bankers Association pages, or
register with Connecticut Bankers Association site or services, a cookie helps Connecticut Bankers Association
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same Connecticut Bankers Association Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Connecticut Bankers Association
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Connecticut Bankers Association services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Connecticut Bankers Association secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. Connecticut Bankers Association secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Connecticut Bankers Association will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. Connecticut Bankers Association encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how Connecticut Bankers Association is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
Connecticut Bankers Association welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that Connecticut Bankers Association has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact Connecticut Bankers Association at ApteanOperations-GODNN@aptean.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
